So mind you, when you configure BitLocker on a Windows server domain on prem,
and you configure BitLocker to save the recovery key, also in Azure Active Directory,
you should be able to set Azure Active Directory or your Endpoints Manager to be able to find your recovery key.
So let's say you have a situation where a user tries to log on on its device and is working from home,
and you are not around the office at the moment, and the user calls you and says,
"Well, I have a problem, I cannot tell you, I says my device,
and you don't have your device with you, as an honest, straight up, but you have your mobile device."
You can still access the Azure Active Directory online, and the cloud, and then from there,
if I go to the bottom of my left, let me just go to Azure Active Directory first of all,
and here you can see we have devices, so another device is let me just click on all the devices,
and then we have our Windows 11 operating system, and another Windows 11 operating system.
You can see we have the BitLocker key preview, and here we go.
You can see the BitLocker ID, if I show the recovery key, you can see that the BitLocker recovery key,
we have here for this device, and you can't only just get the BitLocker recovery key from your Azure Active Directory admin center,
but you can also, if we go to endpoint manager, and from here, I go to the devices,
and from devices, if I click on our Windows operating system devices, and here we have our device,
our Windows 11, 0, 4, and I click on it.
So, if I just did this for the first time, definitely, you're going to take some time for it, which is okay, where is the key located.
What I've been doing, there's a lot, a lot so I know it's not the way the key is either the recovery key keys for operating system,
and it's not like the Azure Active Directory, we can do a show, recovery key, and here we go.
You can see we have the center recovery key for our device, so we can just copy that,
and then I can decide to go to notepad, and paste it there.
So, that is how you get your recovery key from your endpoint manager, and also from Azure Active Directory for your users.